const dayTwelveQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "If one mistakenly eats or drinks while fasting (obligatory fasting), will he re fast that day?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Sacred months are Muharram, Rajab, Dhul Hijjah and ……..?",
    options: ["Ramadan", "Sha’ban", "Rabi’ul Awwal", "Dhul Qadah", "Shawwal"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "When did the fasting in the month of Ramadan become compulsory?",
    options: [
      "a year before hijrah",
      "2nd year of hijrah",
      "6th year of hijrah",
      "10th year of hijrah",
      "12th year of hijrah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Does using eye-drops while fasting vitiate fasting?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it in shari’ah that widows should wear black dresses for mourning their dead husband?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Station at which pilgrims on the hajj is required to put on Ihram (Mawaqitul Hajj) is of two kinds, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Miqat of time and Miqat of place",
      "Miqat of Ihram and Miqat of Tawaf",
      "Miqat of Safa and Miqat of Marwa",
      "Miqat of Qudum and Miqat of Ifaadah",
      "Miqat of Hajj and Miqat of Umrah",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Iddha (mandatory waiting period) for a divorce woman?",
    options: [
      "4 months",
      "3 months",
      "4 months and 10 days",
      "3 months and 10 days",
      "4 months and 13 days",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Iddha (mandatory waiting period) for a widow?",
    options: [
      "4 months",
      "3 months",
      "4 months and 10 days",
      "3 months and 10 days",
      "4 months and 13 days",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A menstruating woman will perform all act of Hajj except……………………….till she is clean.",
    options: ["Ihram", "Jamrah", "Tawaf", "Sa’i", "staying at ‘Arafah"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The most liked kind of voluntary fasting to Allaah is fasting of ……………",
    options: [
      "Ayamul bid (white days)",
      "six days of Shawwal",
      "Sha’ban",
      "‘Arafah day",
      "Prophet Daud",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Kinds of Tawaf (Circumabulation) are: Tawaful Qudum, Tawaful Ifaadah and ……..?",
    options: [
      "Tawaful Ifrad",
      "Tawaful Jadid",
      "Tawaful Akhir",
      "Tawaful Wida’",
      "Tawaful Talbiyah",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Pillars of Hajj (according to Jamhuur) are four, namely: Ihram, wuquf bil ‘Arafah, As Sha’i between Safa and Marwa and ……",
    options: ["Jamrah", "Tawaf Ifadah", "Tawaf Qudum", "Tawaf Wada’", "Umrah"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Zakah of Cows; For every 30 cows = 1 young cow For every 40 cows = …………………",
    options: [
      "one-year old cow",
      "2 young cows",
      "two-year-old cow",
      "3 young cows",
      "three-year-old cow",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Is it allowed to say the intention?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is there anything like Jumu’ah nafilah (Jumu’ah voluntary prayer) before jumu’ah obligatory prayer?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];

export default dayTwelveQuestions;
